https://www.greekpeak.net/privacy-policy/

Search Site
×
Search for:
BookNow
HOURSEVENTSCONTACTABOUTNEWSLETTERPLAN YOUR STAYAccommodationsBook A RoomStay PackagesAmenities & Guest ServicesDiningTestimonialsArcadia VillageOwner Log-InSKI & RIDELift TicketsSeason Pass Details & PerksTrail Maps & Mountain StatsLessonsIndy PassYouth Skiing & Terrain Based LearningCross-Country SkiingSchool ProgramsCollege PE ProgramsNASTAR RacingSANYEquipment Rentals & RepairAdaptive Snow SportsGreek Peak Ski ClubGreek Peak Ski PatrolRefund PolicyCurrent Conditions & WebcamsWATERPARKPurchase TicketsBirthday Parties & EventsWaterpark Deals & DiscountsADVENTURE CENTERAdventure Center Deals & PackagesBirthday Parties & EventsAttractions & RatesSPAReserve Your ServiceSpa Services & PackagesWEDDING & EVENTSWeddingsComplimentary TouchesCorporate Meetings & EventsTeam BuildingBirthday Parties & EventsVenuesBIKE PARKCross-Country BikingDownhill Mountain Biking
broken clouds
29°F
AboutAboutHours of OperationNewsletter Sign-UpContact UsPlan Your StayPlan Your StayAccommodationsStay PackagesAmenities & Guest ServicesDiningArcadia VillageTestimonialsOwner Log-InEvent CalendarSki & RideSeason Pass Details & PerksCurrent Conditions & WebcamsTrail Maps & Mountain StatsLessonsYouth Skiing & Terrain Based LearningCross-Country SkiingSchool ProgramsSchool ProgramsCollege PE ProgramsNASTAR RacingSANYEquipment Rentals & RepairIndy PassAdaptive Snow SportsRefund PolicyGreek Peak Ski ClubGreek Peak Ski PatrolWaterparkWaterpark Deals & DiscountsBirthday Parties & EventsPurchase TicketsOutdoor Adventure CenterOutdoor Adventure CenterAdventure Center Deals & PackagesBirthday Parties & EventsAttractions & RatesSpa & FitnessSpa & FitnessReserve Your ServiceSpa Services & PackagesWeddings & EventsWeddings & EventsWeddingsComplimentary TouchesCorporate Meetings & EventsTeam BuildingBirthday Parties & EventsVenuesBike ParkCross-Country BikingDownhill Mountain Biking
Privacy Policy—
Your privacy is very important to us. Accordingly, we have developed this Policy for you to understand how we collect, use, communicate, and disclose and make use of personal information. The following outlines our privacy policy:
Before or at the time of collecting personal information, we will identify the purposes for which information is being collected.
We will collect and use personal information solely with the objective of fulfilling those purposes specified by us and for other compatible purposes, unless we obtain the consent of the individual concerned or as required by law.
We will only retain personal information as long as necessary for the fulfillment of those purposes.
We will collect personal information by lawful and fair means and, where appropriate, with the knowledge or consent of the individual concerned.
Personal data should be relevant to the purposes for which it is to be used, and, to the extent necessary for those purposes, should be accurate, complete, and up-to-date.
We will protect personal information by reasonable security safeguards against loss or theft, as well as unauthorized access, disclosure, copying, use or modification.
We will make readily available to customers information about our policies and practices relating to the management of personal information.
We are committed to conducting our business in accordance with these principles to ensure that the confidentiality of personal information is protected and maintained.
Media Policy—
If you are a working member of the press and plan to visit Greek Peak Mountain Resort, please let us know in advance so that we can be of assistance to you. News Media members can ski or ride for free at any time during the season. To arrange for free tickets, lessons, and rentals, contact us in advance. You will need to bring your business card for verification.
Drone Policy—
Due to safety and privacy concerns, Greek Peak Mountain Resort prohibits the operation or use on or above resort property of unmanned aerial systems, or drones, by the general public—including model aircraft by recreational users and hobbyists.  This prohibition includes drones used for filming or videotaping, as well as any drone use by media or journalists operating above or within the area boundaries.
This prohibition extends to any devices launched or operated from resort property, as well as any launched from private property outside of the resort boundaries. Please contact a resort representative if you have any questions.
Any authorized operation of drones on or above resort property will be governed by Federal Aviation Administration (FAA) rules and regulations, local law enforcement, as well as those policies separately established by this resort, which may include certification, training, insurance coverage, indemnification requirements, and waivers or releases of liability.
Any violation of this policy may involve suspension of your access privileges to the resort, or the revocation of your season pass, as well as confiscation of any  prohibited equipment, and may subject violators to any liability for damages, including, but not limited to, damages for trespass, violations of privacy, and physical injuries to persons and/or property, as well as legal fees.
Adaptive Devices Policy—
As of 5/2/2011, Greek Peak has adopted a “no motorized” policy for the public. The use of any power-driven devices or vehicles by the public, including devices used by individuals with mobility disabilities that were not primarily designed for use by individuals with disabilities, would pose safety hazards to individuals using the trails for hiking and mountain biking. This assessment is based on the size, weight, dimensions, and speed of these devices; the potential for collisions with other visitors; the high volume of traffic on the trails; and the substantial risk of serious impacts on natural resources caused by these vehicles.
The Resort allows individuals with mobility disabilities to use wheelchairs and manually powered mobility aids, such as walkers, crutches, canes, braces, or other similar devices designed for use by individuals with mobility disabilities in areas open to pedestrian use.
The Ski Area allows the use of adaptive devices or other ”manually-powered mobility aids” designed for use on the slopes. Adaptive devices are any specialized equipment that has been designed and manufactured primarily for use by individuals who have disabilities, including without limitation mono-skis, bi skis, outriggers, and sit-skis. The Ski Area rental facility offers or will arrange for any adaptive equipment that meets this definition when requested for rental in advance by individuals wanting to enjoy winter sports at our resort.
Inclement Weather Policy for the Outdoor Adventure Center—
The Adventure Center is an outdoor facility and will operate as usual in the rain, snow, etc. However, we may be required to delay or shut down operations due to high winds, ice, thunder, lightning or other dangerous weather conditions. Guests will be safely returned to the Adventure Center base building to wait for conditions to clear up.
If the area is closed completely for the remainder of the business day or if the delay lasts more than 1 hour, the following can be considered:
No refunds will be issued
Rain checks can be issued at the discretion of the Manager on Duty depending on how much of a given activity was completed
The same policy applies if you are dissatisfied with the conditions of any Adventure Center activity
SIGN UP FOR NEWS & OFFERS
SIGN UP
CONTACT USName *Email *Message *WebsiteSubmit
Greek Peak Mountain Resort
2000 NYS Rt. 392Cortland, NY 13045Adventure Center: 1856 NYS Rt. 392Hope Lake Lodge & Waterpark: 2177 Clute Road*Pricing and content subject to change without notice**Greek Peak adheres to all NYS COVID-19 mandates and directives*
800-955-2754
Contact Us
Driving Directions
Quicks Links
EmploymentDonation RequestsPreferred PartnersTerms & ConditionsPrivacy PolicyAccessibility Statement
FacebookInstagramTwitter
Greek Peak Holdings, LLC. - Christine C. Meier, Broker - 2000 NYS RT 392 - Cortland, NY 13045
